<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Where everybody knows my name</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Where everybody knows my name</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 08:47:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3-23-21 Picks</title>
      <link>/trade/3-23-21-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 08:47:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-23-21-picks/</guid>
      <description>Patience. That is what it takes to make good trades. Well that and a little bit of money helps too.
Since last week I could not find any positions that interested me. Everything was either to over bought and not falling yet or not over sold yet. Then Monday evening comes along where everything in the crypto space, save for a select few, was in free fall. Bitcoin dropped from $57k to $54 and may have even touched $53.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-19-21 Picks</title>
      <link>/trade/3-19-21-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 08:33:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-19-21-picks/</guid>
      <description>What went wrong?????? That is the big question and it is probably the least significant answer too. Why? Because it does not matter why something moved in one direction or the other, it only matters that you failed to plan for either case. And that is truly what went wrong. It does not matter that the Dow, the Nasdaq, the dollar, or whatever influenced the trade one way or the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-18-21 Picks</title>
      <link>/trade/3-18-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 07:02:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-18-21/</guid>
      <description>Today is all about Cardano ($ADA)!
Trading on Coinbase Pro starts at 9AM PST (12PM EST) from there this could be very wild ride to the top. There is some analysis out there that shows a possible run up to $3.50. But to be realistic, there is also analysis out there that shows it could only go to at most $1.86. Both projections were based on the last two coins to be listed on Coinbase Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-17-21 Picks - UPDATED</title>
      <link>/trade/3-17-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 08:30:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-17-21/</guid>
      <description>Not much to trade today. There is lots of red on the board; however at 8AM nothing is down significantly, so we wait.
The Fed ends day 2 of the FOMC meeting. My expectation is that Powell makes a statement that says they are still not worried about inflation, which will send shockwaves across all markets. The 10y will rise more than it has already (currently it is at 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-16-21 Picks</title>
      <link>/trade/3-16-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 09:40:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-16-21/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to start posting the trades I think are interesting to my site. This is not investment advice, so do with it as you wish and take it what it is for.
Today I have my eye on a two cryptos.
UNIUSDT
UNI has tumbled 14.5% since the 13th on the 4h time frame. MarketCipher B shows a green dot, and while not a glowing green dot, on this time frame it should not be ignored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>23 day Bear Market</title>
      <link>/post/23day-bear-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 17:24:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/23day-bear-market/</guid>
      <description>The chart above is $BTC:USDT 1 Day timeline.
It took 23 days from breaking the ATH on Dec 16 to the new ATH on Jan 8. From there the price fell $28,686 at its lowest. Then it went sideways. On Day 23 the price posted one more red candle and then it has been a steady climb up again.
I am not going to analyze this for you, but there seems to be a pattern here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Element</title>
      <link>/element/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 16:27:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/element/</guid>
      <description>Hey, you are in the &amp;ldquo;in crowed&amp;rdquo;. Bookmark this page because there are no external links back to it.
To connect to the Matrix server you can use the web browser client by going to https://element.normanbauer.io and signup there.
After you create or connect an account, you can download the Element client from the App Store of Google Play and login there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I DO NOT CONSENT</title>
      <link>/post/privacy-starts-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 02:09:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/privacy-starts-now/</guid>
      <description>In the last couple of weeks I have been giving serious consideration to deleting Facebook. Just blowing away my entire account. However I have decided not to for the moment, as I like the benefit of keeping in touch with friends and family and for better or worse, Facebook is still where they all are.
However after finding out why all iPhone users were logged out of Facebook I did make the decision to delete all vestiges from my iPhone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing to See Here Move Along</title>
      <link>/post/nothing-to-see-here-move-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 08:26:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nothing-to-see-here-move-along/</guid>
      <description>Mary Daly on Blooberg reminds be of the scene from The Naked Gun where Lesly Neilson is telling everyone to move along, there is nothing to see here, while the building is on fire.
Or even and even better meme is Bahgdad Bob
The whopper of a lie starts at the 5:40 mark in the video when Michael McKee asks her about inflation. Check it out.
I feel bad for her because the reality is she can&amp;rsquo;t come out and speak the truth because if she did what she says would tank everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Manipulation</title>
      <link>/post/btc-manipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 06:19:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/btc-manipulation/</guid>
      <description>Imagine if you will that the US consumer is consuming more than 18x the amount of refined oil that can be produced in the US per day, yet the price at the pump for a gallon of gas is falling and it&amp;rsquo;s not just falling it is tumbling.
That is the exact scenario that is being played out right now in the crypto market. 907 new coins are minted each day and Grayscale bought 16,000 in one day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Term Limits? No!</title>
      <link>/post/term-limits-no/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 19:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/term-limits-no/</guid>
      <description>The post Omnibus Spending Bill fallout has the left and the right both justified and united in their anger at Congress. This righteous anger has again created new calls for term limits. While I am sympathetic to the call, I also have to oppose such calls. I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best to explain why term limits are not a fix and will only make the problem worse and I will offer two options that will actually change things and go a long way to restoring the true idea of governance that was and is still unique to the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook OG Tags</title>
      <link>/post/facebook-og-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 13:05:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/facebook-og-tags/</guid>
      <description>Facebook introduced the https://ogp.me format however long ago it was, I am not sure. For me, as a website developer and content creator, the OG format is always one of those things I forget about until I&amp;rsquo;ve published the site and go to share the first post (note to self to add that to the check list). When Facebook does not parse my content I get my sad face on because yet again I have forgotten to add the OG tags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Google Purge</title>
      <link>/post/another-google-purge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 14:52:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/another-google-purge/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not clear to me who is running Google anymore. Google has decided to purge two programming language groups. comp.lang.forth &amp;amp; comp.lang.lisp
Of importance to me is the purge of Lisp. Lisp is one of the oldest programming languages. My favorite editor Emacs is written in a fork of Lisp (elisp). Contrary to what the twenty somethings at Google may think, lisp is still used today. However more important than the fact that it is still used is the historical value the threads themselves provide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 15:39:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/links/</guid>
      <description>Links to sites I like.
 Wye Oak Mobile Device Repair Miss Constitution Zerohedge Planet Ubuntu Lew Rockwell Economic Policy Journal Cointelegraph  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M2</title>
      <link>/m2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 12:45:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/m2/</guid>
      <description>The chart below is produced using the numbers from The St Louis Federal Reserve Bank. They are in charge of reporting on the money supply.
On March 16, 2020 the M2 stock was 15,726 billion USD.
As of July 27th, 2020 the M2 stock was 18286 billion USD.
That represents a 14% increase in the money supply in a matter of 4 months.
 REAL INFLATION = 25.14% from 04/16/20 - 02/01/21    M2 Money Supply - St Louis Fed   What is M- Stock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozialla VPN</title>
      <link>/post/mozialla-vpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 11:20:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mozialla-vpn/</guid>
      <description>The new broke to me about three days ago that Mozilla has finally thrown their hat into the VPN ring. Yea!!!!
A few years ago Mozilla found itself in the unique position as the only alternative browser to Google Chrome other then Apple&amp;rsquo;s Safari. Opera had dropped their rendering engine in 2013 (Called Presto) in favor of Google Chrome&amp;rsquo;s Blink rendering engine. Internet Explorer was abandoned by Microsoft and rebuilt from scratch with Google Chrome&amp;rsquo;s Blink and rebranded as Edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 18:20:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/media/</guid>
      <description>I recently had my first radio interview and I hope it is not the last. Given that, I thought it would be a good idea to keep a running tally.
 Kyle O&amp;rsquo;Donnell and I speak about what I would like to see the LP take the lead on in 2021
 July 22, 2020 - Colorado Front Range Hour on 1360khnc.com The Roar of The Rockies. Hosts Jason, Bryan, Glen have me on to discuss the Portland Protests and Constitutionality of federal police.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 18:20:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Norman Bauer. I am the owner of Wye Oak Mobile Device Repair and Wye Oak Business Solutions.
I have many interests such as my wife &amp;amp; our kids (2 girls), outdoors stuff, canning, long term food storage, cryptocurrency, precious metals, Austrian Economics, libertarianism, agorism, the US Constitution, electronics, programming, computer repair, virtualization, Linux, Linux Containers, networking, books, UFO&amp;rsquo;s, music, radio&amp;rsquo;s (CB, AM, Shortwave, and some HAM stuff too), and a lot more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 1st</title>
      <link>/post/the-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:31:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-1st/</guid>
      <description>Here is the first post. I am leaving this as a sample and do not intend to get rid of it.
This site is a work in progress. It is meant for my pleasure and to server whatever ends I think are needed. You&amp;rsquo;ll probably find topics that range from libertarianism to technology and all things inbetween.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>