<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Where everybody knows my name</title>
    <link>https://normanbauer.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Where everybody knows my name</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:31:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://normanbauer.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://normanbauer.io/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 18:20:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://normanbauer.io/media/</guid>
      <description>I recently had my first radio interview and I hope it is not the last. Given that, I thought it would be a good idea to keep a running tally.
 July 22, 2020 - Colorado Front Range Hour on 1360khnc.com The Roar of The Rockies. Hosts Jason, Bryan, Glen have me on to discuss the Portland Protests and Constitutionality of federal police. Click here to listen to the interview.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://normanbauer.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 18:20:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://normanbauer.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Norman Bauer. I am the owner of Wye Oak Mobile Device Repair and Wye Oak Business Solutions.
I have many interests such as, my wife &amp;amp; our kids (2 girls), outdoors stuff, canning, long term food storage, cryptocurrency, presciouse metals, Austrian Economomics, libertarinism, agorism, the US Constitution, electronics, programming, computer repair, virtualization, Linux, Linux Containers, networking, books, UFO&amp;rsquo;s, music, radio&amp;rsquo;s (CB, AM, Shortwave, and some HAM stuff too), and a lot more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 1st</title>
      <link>https://normanbauer.io/post/the-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:31:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://normanbauer.io/post/the-1st/</guid>
      <description>Here is the first post. I am leaving this as a sample and do not intend to get rid of it.
This site is a work in progress. It is meant for my pleasure and to server whatever ends I think are needed. You&amp;rsquo;ll probably find topics that range from libertarianism to technology and all things inbetween.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>