<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Where everybody knows my name</title>
    <link>https://normanbauer.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Where everybody knows my name</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 15:39:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://normanbauer.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://normanbauer.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 15:39:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://normanbauer.io/links/</guid>
      <description>Links to sites I like.
Wye Oak Mobile Device Repair Miss Constitution Zerohedge Planet Ubuntu Lew Rockwell Economic Policy Journal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M2</title>
      <link>https://normanbauer.io/m2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 12:45:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://normanbauer.io/m2/</guid>
      <description>The above chart is produced using the numbers from The St Louis Federal Reserve Bank. They are in charge of reporting on the money supply.
On March 16, 2020 the M2 stock was 15,726 billion USD.
As of July 13th, 2020 the M2 stock was 18399 billion USD.
That represents a 14% increase in the money supply in a matter of 4 months.
What is M- Stock? In banking the supply of money and credit is broken down into three catagories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozialla VPN</title>
      <link>https://normanbauer.io/post/mozialla-vpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 11:20:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://normanbauer.io/post/mozialla-vpn/</guid>
      <description>The new broke to me about three days ago that Mozilla has finally thrown their hat into the VPN ring. Yea!!!!
A few years ago Mozilla found itself in the unique position as the only alternative browser to Google Chrome other then Apple&amp;rsquo;s Safari. Opera had dropped their rendering engine in 2013 (Called Presto) in favor of Google Chrome&amp;rsquo;s Blink rendering engine. Internet Explorer was abandoned by Microsoft and rebuilt from scratch with Google Chrome&amp;rsquo;s Blink and rebranded as Edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://normanbauer.io/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 18:20:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://normanbauer.io/media/</guid>
      <description>I recently had my first radio interview and I hope it is not the last. Given that, I thought it would be a good idea to keep a running tally.
 July 22, 2020 - Colorado Front Range Hour on 1360khnc.com The Roar of The Rockies. Hosts Jason, Bryan, Glen have me on to discuss the Portland Protests and Constitutionality of federal police. Click here to listen to the interview.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://normanbauer.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 18:20:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://normanbauer.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Norman Bauer. I am the owner of Wye Oak Mobile Device Repair and Wye Oak Business Solutions.
I have many interests such as, my wife &amp;amp; our kids (2 girls), outdoors stuff, canning, long term food storage, cryptocurrency, precious metals, Austrian Economics, libertarianism, agorism, the US Constitution, electronics, programming, computer repair, virtualization, Linux, Linux Containers, networking, books, UFO&amp;rsquo;s, music, radio&amp;rsquo;s (CB, AM, Shortwave, and some HAM stuff too), and a lot more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 1st</title>
      <link>https://normanbauer.io/post/the-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:31:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://normanbauer.io/post/the-1st/</guid>
      <description>Here is the first post. I am leaving this as a sample and do not intend to get rid of it.
This site is a work in progress. It is meant for my pleasure and to server whatever ends I think are needed. You&amp;rsquo;ll probably find topics that range from libertarianism to technology and all things inbetween.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>