<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trades on Where everybody knows my name</title>
    <link>/trade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trades on Where everybody knows my name</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 08:47:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/trade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3-23-21 Picks</title>
      <link>/trade/3-23-21-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 08:47:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-23-21-picks/</guid>
      <description>Patience. That is what it takes to make good trades. Well that and a little bit of money helps too.
Since last week I could not find any positions that interested me. Everything was either to over bought and not falling yet or not over sold yet. Then Monday evening comes along where everything in the crypto space, save for a select few, was in free fall. Bitcoin dropped from $57k to $54 and may have even touched $53.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-19-21 Picks</title>
      <link>/trade/3-19-21-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 08:33:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-19-21-picks/</guid>
      <description>What went wrong?????? That is the big question and it is probably the least significant answer too. Why? Because it does not matter why something moved in one direction or the other, it only matters that you failed to plan for either case. And that is truly what went wrong. It does not matter that the Dow, the Nasdaq, the dollar, or whatever influenced the trade one way or the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-18-21 Picks</title>
      <link>/trade/3-18-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 07:02:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-18-21/</guid>
      <description>Today is all about Cardano ($ADA)!
Trading on Coinbase Pro starts at 9AM PST (12PM EST) from there this could be very wild ride to the top. There is some analysis out there that shows a possible run up to $3.50. But to be realistic, there is also analysis out there that shows it could only go to at most $1.86. Both projections were based on the last two coins to be listed on Coinbase Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-17-21 Picks - UPDATED</title>
      <link>/trade/3-17-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 08:30:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-17-21/</guid>
      <description>Not much to trade today. There is lots of red on the board; however at 8AM nothing is down significantly, so we wait.
The Fed ends day 2 of the FOMC meeting. My expectation is that Powell makes a statement that says they are still not worried about inflation, which will send shockwaves across all markets. The 10y will rise more than it has already (currently it is at 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-16-21 Picks</title>
      <link>/trade/3-16-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 09:40:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/trade/3-16-21/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to start posting the trades I think are interesting to my site. This is not investment advice, so do with it as you wish and take it what it is for.
Today I have my eye on a two cryptos.
UNIUSDT
UNI has tumbled 14.5% since the 13th on the 4h time frame. MarketCipher B shows a green dot, and while not a glowing green dot, on this time frame it should not be ignored.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>